I uh I'm married guys I uh 31
[Applause]
years it's a lot of Applause you don't
know her she's
[Music]
uh it's a challenge
sometimes I love her to death I'm not
going anywhere cuz let's be honest I
don't have options this is uh this is
what commitment looks like folks this is
this is coming home at 7:00 every night
with maybe A Slice of Cheesecake you
know cuz if your guy has a six-pack
ladies check his phone that's all I'm
[Music]
saying that's just me hating on fit guys
that's
all that's just all that is you know I
love her man she's uh she's a great
person she's she's a nurse she works
nights I think she's a nurse I'm not
really sure where she goes uh she n of
my business really they they pay her in
cash I don't know what kind of hospital
this is
I she hates that joke she's
like I uh I I I always don't I I don't I
joke around too much I don't turn it off
you know what I mean I'm OB just
Clowning Around the other day we're
driving home from dinner and it must
have just rained the road's real foggy I
go what if we hit something and we think
it's a deer but it's not it turns out
it's a
unicorn that is the dumbest thing I've
ever
heard stop talking and I'm like just
hear me out dude you know orns are
magical if I did hit one I would just
gra drag him to the side of the road
he'd be so grateful he grant us two
wishes what would you do with your
wish she
goes I wish I had a husband that didn't
believe in unicorns and uh and I giggle
all the way home cuz she's upset over an
accident that can't happen on a thing
that doesn't exist it's a non-issue you
know it's not a huge fan of my comedy
bro I'm not going to I'm not going to
lie to you like I bought a dream catcher
and I put it over my side of the bed and
she cut all the strings out I'm like
that
is you're just hating at this point that
is it's not
nice we argue over dumb stuff like which
way does the toilet paper come off the
roll over the tops you only that makes
sense to me am I
right any underhands any there's always
one I
just I don't have that kind of time man
I just want to slap and go I
got I got stuff to do be looking for
seams like some
lunatic she
um she caught me sleeping on the couch
uh the other day CU that's what guys do
sometimes you know and uh she goes you
know you can stay down there all night
I'm like I don't mind sleeping on the
couch I don't know ladies it's not a
punishment to make your guys sleep on
the couch it's but I got tired of
walking around the house looking like a
lost toddler with a pillow and a
blanket so we're not get punished I just
I bought another couch I guess is what
I'm trying to say and I put it next to
her side of the
bed and I just touch her with my feet
and stuff I
just drives are
crazy this is pretty awesome
man I um I don't know man I just been
through some challenges recently I uh
turned 52 in August and uh I know I
don't look it that's just cuz the Fat's
pushing the wrinkles out that
is that's the only reason that is
cholesterol I uh I'm going to die pretty
I guess is what I'm trying to
say No I um my wife goes Ling our
insurance is changing I need you to go
in and get a physical and get this
figured out all right so uh I go in and
I didn't want to go CU last time I went
the guy yelled at me told me to lose a
bunch of weight and I didn't and uh so I
knew it was coming all right so I go to
the appointment 7:00 F out the medical
history handed to the lady behind the
counter and she must been having a bad
day I don't know what her deal was but
she snatches the paperwork I wait
another 15 minutes and they call me from
the the door she's like Mr Rodriguez I'm
like here she goes come on I'm like okay
settle down as soon as we walk through
the door there's the
scale like here we go
she just can you get on the scale I'm
like all right you know and I hold my
breath like it's going to help me way
less you ever do that
nonsense and she's moving the thing and
you ever had them move that thing to the
next 50 lb increment at 7:30 in the
morning it's not a great day way not a
great way to start the day off C Clank
and then she goes wow son wow I'm like
what she's like 293 I'm like my keys
were in my
pocket she goes it's not to Keys fat boy
get in the
back doctor be with you in a second I'm
in the back room 20 30 40 minutes come
by I'm like nobody's coming this is
ridiculous man I got bored and I got
sleepy you know that exam table they
have there
right they have that butcher paper they
had a new roll it's like you're going to
make me wait this is this is what's
happening
this I took the whole roll off the thing
I made a nest in the middle of exam room
3 I I got in the nest like a giant baby
bird snuggled in and fell asleep you
know I wake up 40 minutes later and it's
freezing so I rip some off and I put
over my shoulder like Grandma's
sweater the guy walks in he's like what
is going on and I was in the
syrups I got bored you're not going to
leave me alone for 3 hours I'm not going
to play with the
equipment so they figured out listen you
got to go get a a cardiac stress test
you know I was having heart palpitations
and uh so I make an appointment I go see
that guy and um I knew it was going to
be a bad day cuz uh the I I thought you
would just go in and take your blood
pressure or something and you're in and
out you know and the lady comes in the
back she goes sir I need you to take
your shirt off for this procedure I'm
like are you sure she's like yeah that's
how it works I need you take your shirt
off and then I'm kind of old school I
got a hairy chest she had to shave
little blocks on my chest and glue the
leads on and I'm remember looking down
going oh this is just this is gross I
got a I gotta lose weight and it look
like I have mange this is
horrible and all the wires go to a box
and the box was on a belt and she could
have just handed it to me and let me put
it on but she leaned behind me with the
Buckle in one hand and just threw it to
the other
side that's unnecessary that
is and she's strapped it on real tight
it's digging in the meat I this is
horrible man she goes get on the
treadmill I'm like what
for she she goes the stress test I'm
like I'm already stressed out this
is she I get out she fires this thing up
to 12 miles an hour I've never run this
fast in my life right she starts angling
it up like the Russian and Rocky
4 and I imagine that's what I would look
like if he was overweight and crying
that's what
[Music]
uh I was fine at that time that was that
time I was okay that was pretty
recently uh it gets worse man I uh
Father's Day 2019 I'm on stage
performing at a theater and I break out
in a cold sweat like I'm I normally
sweat a fair amount but it it was like a
suspicious amount of sweat like like R
Kelly standing outside of a high school
it was a guilty amount of sweat you know
what I mean it
was and it turns out I was having having
a heart attack on stage
guys yeah I'm not trying to scare
anybody spoiler alert I didn't die so
there's a good ending there's a good
ending right and uh so uh I leave the
show I finish the show cuz I'm an idiot
you know and uh go home and I tell my
wife I go I think I'm having a heart
attack she's like yeah you're probably
just dehydrated or whatever right so
she's watching me and know I'm kneeling
on the floor with my chest in the
cushions and I'm kind of Moaning right
and she goes oh man she calls my son
she's like hey get the box I'm like the
Box my son comes down with a box in the
box has a little bottle of nitroglycerin
tablets I'm like you had nitroglycerin
on
standby she goes look at yourself man
this we knew this this was inevitable we
we knew it was coming we I'm like we're
going to talk about this later you
know 5 minutes later I feel like a
million bucks they rushed me to the
hospital you know and uh so you know
it's they confirmed it heart attack
right and uh so Sunday sitting around
this is Father's Day Sunday 2019 Monday
morning the nurse comes in she goes Mr
Rodriguez do you have any questions I'm
like no I'm good she goes okay well the
tech is going to come in and she's going
to tighten you up for the procedure I'm
like what she goes you know she's going
to prep your area and I'm like what and
she could have just said that they were
going to Shear me like a young lamb it
was when they started I was like can I
do myself is that a she's like no you're
on blood thinners it's very dangerous
I'm like listen I I've been married a
long time and I'm a little shy and it's
it's freezing in here it is
so so
cold she goes you'll be
okay they will me into the lab and I'm
like how's everybody doing and then
splash ice cold mop full antiseptic
right at Ground Zero you
know like is this supposed to burn like
this this is spicy she's like yeah you
going to be okay and I'm like I I can't
take it man so I'm trying to cool myself
off by
but the breath is hitting my belly and
shooting up this way the lady's bangs
are moving I'm like this is
horrible I was like Miss is there any
way that you
could she's like what no you're going to
be
fine you're going to be
fine 90% blockage man they found one
they put one stin in so I'm fine so I'm
good no no more coffee and no more no
more fried no more happiness really is
what they
said and then what are they do they make
a wall of cake I'm
like I'm like that's the most delicious
looking rock wall I've ever seen in my
life if the the current opened any
sooner you would have caught me on that
wall trying
to like a fat Spider-Man that was
[Music]
uh